# RYAN ROSALES

**User Experience Designer and Prototyper** 

Creative and highly-motivated User Experience Designer with a strong foundation in Graphic Design and Typography. I specialize in experience design and prototyping to provide time-efficient and cost-effective design processes for businesses. Currently focused on learning and building AR/VR experiences.

Portfolio: https://ryanrosales.com/ Email: ryancrosales1@gmail.com

**Linkedin**: ryancrosales **Phone**: (559) 283-5997

### **Experience**

#### **Lennar Corporation** | User Interface Designer

February, 2021 - April, 2021

Responsible for designing web pages for various residential communities in the San Francisco, Bay Area.

#### Infinite Peripherals | Design Intern

October, 2019 - January, 2020

Designed the UI and 20-foot marketing display for NRF in collaboration with the design, engineering, and marketing teams. Responsible for the UI design and direction of product landing pages in collaboration with Otterbox and Oracle. Worked in Sketch to design assets and manage design systems.

#### Freelance | UX/UI Designer

May, 2019 - August, 2020

Worked with product management to research, design and deliver a mobile app for a automotive company. Designed and delivered a personal website for a Senior Full-Stack Developer. Worked with a startup in Irvine, California to redesign their landing page and spearheaded the design of a web app MVP.

### **Education**

#### Introduction to XR: VR, AR, and MR Foundations

Coursera. Issued Jan. 2021.

No Expiration Date.

#### California State University, Fullerton

August, 2017 - May, 2020

Graphic and Interactive Design Specialization

**Relevant Coursework**: Intro to Psychology, Web and Interactive Design, Typography A, B and C.

#### Skills

Design	Research	Languages	Tech
AR/VR Web/Mobile Typography Wireframing Prototyping 3D	Interviews Surveys Journey mapping Usability testing	HTML/CSS	Figma Adobe CC Principle Unity 3D Blender A-Frame Vuforia ARFoundation

### **Selected Projects**

## Healthcare Training (Virtual Reality)

May, 2021 - June, 2021

Managed and spearheaded the end-toend design process. Executed 3D modeling in Blender and user interfaces and programming in Unity. Tested prototypes at varying fidelities to validate concepts. Conducted primary and secondary research, and 1-on-1 interviews.

# Career Counseling (Mobile App)

May, 2021

Concerted secondary and primary research, survey, and competitive analysis to validate the weight of the problem. Performed userflows, user interface design, prototyping and testing.

# Crunchyroll (Website Redesign)

August, 2020

Performed primary research and surveys to identify user pain points.

Conducted secondary and market research to align solutions to current business values. Executed user interface design and prototyping.